chictopia.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Chictopia

**1.                   ****Overview** ****

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") informs you about the personal information collected about users of the online service accessible via the Website located at www.Chictopia.com and related URLs (the "Service") and how such information may be used or disclosed by Chictopia.com, LLC. ("Chictopia"). ****

The term "You" (and its variants) refers to You as a user of the Service and the term "Us" (and its variants) refers to Chictopia. 

In operating the Service We collect and may disclose information about You. By accepting the Chictopia.com Terms of Service (“the TOS”), into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference, You acknowledge that you have read and understand this policy, and consent to Our use and disclosure of Your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**2.                   ****Information We Collect**  
  
****

a.       _Personal Information_. In the course of using the Service, you may provide us with personally identifiable information.  This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information on your use of and activities in connection with the Service that may be connected with you (“ **Personal Information** ”).  Personal Information that we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, birth date, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses, physical description and attributes.  Personal Information may also include information you supply to us in the course of using our Site including your preferences, interests, tastes and styles, product preferences, wardrobe, and purchase history.  Other types of content submissions may also contain Personal Information.  For example, photos may show your face, home, school, clothes, or other identifying marks.  Other submissions, such as graphics, avatars, blog entries, and comments may contain data that can be used to identify you, either on their own, or in conjunction with other submissions.

b.      _Automatic Data Collection_. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website.  This information may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, the web page you were visiting immediately before you came to our Site, the search query you submitted to find our Site on a search engine, what features of the Service you use and how you use them, and how you accumulate and spend your ChicPoints.  We also use data collection devices such as "cookies" in certain portions of the Service. "Cookies" are small files placed on Your hard drive that record snippets of Data and which We use to assist Us in providing customized services. Certain features of the Service are only available with the use of a "cookie." We use this information to determine Our visitors' needs, demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve You and other users. Some cookies are "session cookies" meaning that they are automatically deleted from Your hard drive at the end of a session.  Other cookies are persistent, and remain on your hard drive after you conclude your use of the Service.  You are always free not to accept cookies if Your browser permits.

c.       _Third Party Data_. In the course of using the Service, and interacting with third parties encountered therein, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.  Examples of such information include which third parties you interact with, and the nature of those interactions.  We may also use a third party advertising company to serve ads on Our behalf across the Internet that may collect information about Your visits to the Service. This is primarily accomplished through the use of a technology device, commonly referred to as a Web beacon, cookie or an action tag, which is placed on various Web pages within the Service or in an HTML e-mail that allows the third party advertising company to collect information. There may also be a number of services offered by external service providers that help You use the Service. If You choose to use these optional services and in doing so disclose information to the external service providers or grant them permission to collect information about You, then their use of Your information will be governed by their private policies, if any.

**3.                   ****How We Use Personal Information** ****

a.       We may use Personal Information  (i) to provide and improve the Service, including features, content and related services, as well as personalizing your experience, (ii) to administer your account and your use of the Service, (iii) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Service, (iv) to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with features and offers, including advertisements, targeted to your interests, (v) to fulfill requests you may make, (vi) to personalize your experience, (vii) to provide or offer software and/or web site feature updates and product announcements, and (viii) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by us or third parties; (ix) to facilitate follow up and subsequent dealings with third parties listed on the Site, and to enhance their ability to serve you efficiently and effectively; and (x) to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the TOS.  If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications initiated under part (viii) of this paragraph, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in such communications or update your “user preferences” information.

b.      We may use Personal Information We obtained by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to (i) improve Our marketing and promotional efforts, (ii) to analyze usage of the Service, improve Our content and product offerings, and (iii) to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and (iv) to customize the Service content, layout, and features. 

c.       You may, of course, decline to provide certain Personal Information, and you may always revise or remove information you have provided, but then you may not be able to utilize the Site to its fullest potential (See “ **Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Profile** ”, below).

**4.                   ****Our Disclosure of Your Information.** **  **The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we are not in the business of selling Personal Information to others.  We may, from time to time, share your Personal Information as described below.  Generally, we attempt to make such disclosures under terms similar to this Privacy Policy.  
  
****

a.       **_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_** **.** We may be required by law to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties.  We also cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and with third parties to enforce laws, and may disclose any information about You to law enforcement and other government officials as We in Our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with any investigation of fraud or other activity that is illegal or may expose Us, You, or any other third party to liability.

b.      _Other Users._   We will display Your Personal Information in Your profile page and elsewhere in the Service according to the preferences You set in Your account.  Any information You choose to provide should reflect how much You want all other users to know about You.  We recommend that You guard your anonymity and sensitive information and We encourage users to think carefully about what information about themselves and others they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise Your profile information at any time.

c.       _Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control._   We may work with third-party service providers, and provide You information about their offerings through the Site.  We share Personal Information with those third parties in order to enhance their ability to offer and provide you the highest level of service.  We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other entities with whom we have cooperative relationships so that they can send you promotional and other information and engage in any of the activities described in Section 2 above.  This may include financial and billing information shared with Our service providers and to such third parties as We determine necessary in connection with your use of the Service.

d.      Business Transfers and Disclosures.  We may share Personal Information with Our parent, affiliates, or subsidiaries.  We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of Our assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

e.       _Aggregate Data_.  We aggregate Personal Information of Our members and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. Such aggregate data does not include information that could be used to identify You personally. We do not disclose certain information, such as Your name, email address, password, credit card number and bank account number, in such aggregate formats. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on Our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness.

**5.                   ****Your Use of Other Members' Information**  
Our services may include access to instant messaging, forums, blogs, and chat rooms. As a member You have access to other members' Personal Information through Your use of the Service. You may not use such information in any manner that is not authorized by Us and the applicable member. In all cases, You must give members an opportunity to remove their information from Your information databases, including email lists. Under no circumstances may You disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without Our consent and the consent of such other member. You may not contact a member or add a member to any contact list (electronic, telephone, physical mail, or any other form of contact) without that member's express consent. ****

**6.                   ****Third Party Use of Information**  
This Privacy Policy only addresses Our use and disclosure of information We collect from You. If You disclose Your personal information to other parties, whether via the Service or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information You disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of any third parties so You should investigate their policies before You disclose Your personal information to them. ****

**7.                   ****Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time based on changes in the law, Your comments, or Our need to accurately reflect Our data collection and disclosure practices. We will notify you of such revisions by posting the updated policy to our web site, and such revisions shall become effective in accordance with the procedures for revising the TOS. ****

**8.                   ****Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Profile** ****

a.       After registration You can review the information You submitted during registration. For instructions on how to change the information, contact info@chictopia.com. If you provide less Personal Information, or provide inaccurate Personal Information in order to protect your anonymity, you may not be able to utilize the Service to its full potential.  If you completely remove your Personal Information, your account may be removed or disabled.

b.      We may retain in Our files information You have requested be removed from Our active databases for certain purposes, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, to enforce the Terms of Use, and to discourage users from engaging in fraudulent behavior. Moreover, Your Personal Information may never be completely removed from Our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored “back up” systems. You should not expect that all of Your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from Our databases in response to Your request.

c.       To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information.  YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.  If You believe your password has been disclosed to third parties or otherwise compromised in any way You should immediately change Your password.

**9.                   ****Our Commitment to Data Security**

a.       We are very concerned with safeguarding your information.  We employ reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information.  We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Us, and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your transmission of information, We make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems.  However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

**b.       **If We learn of a security systems breach, We may in certain circumstances attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Depending on where you live and the circumstances, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. ****

**10.               ****Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy** ****

a.       We are particularly concerned with safeguarding the privacy of children.  This Service is not directed to children under thirteen (13), and children under thirteen (13) are expressly prohibited from using the Service under the TOS.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided Us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact Us at privacy@chictopia.com.   If We become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, We will delete such information from our files.  IF YOU ARE UNDER THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OF AGE, THEN YOU MAY NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

b.      As part of our commitment to Children’s privacy, We refer the following resources that parents and legal guardians may find useful in monitoring and limiting children’s access to certain types of material on the Internet.  While We do not endorse these products and services, We provide information about them as a public service to our community. 

**                                                               i.      ****“** **OnGuard Online** **,” maintained by the Federal Trade Commission.   <http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html> **

**                                                             ii.      ****WiredSafety** **[http://www.wiredsafety.org](http://www.wiredsafety.org/) **

**                                                           iii.      ****NetSmartz** **[http://www.netsmartz.org](http://www.netsmartz.org/) **

**                                                           iv.      ****The Child Safety Network** **<http://www.csn.org/index.jsp> **

**                                                             v.      ****Control Kids** **[http://www.controlkids.com](http://www.controlkids.com/) **

**                                                           vi.      ****Cyber Sitter** **[http://www.solidoak.com](http://www.solidoak.com/) **

**                                                         vii.      ****Net Nanny** **[http://www.netnanny.com](http://www.netnanny.com/) **

**11.               ****Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@chictopia.com or at: 

**Chictopia**  
5 Third Street, Suite 422  
San Francisco, CA 94105
